mamalovesherbargains.com 2015-09-05

# Disclosure & Privacy Policies | This Mama Loves

**DISCLOSURE POLICY:**

_This policy is valid from 26 May 2010_

_This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact me here._

_This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation._

_This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content._ __

_The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question._

_This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest._

_To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org_

_We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:  [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)_

**PRIVACY POLICY:**

This policy is valid from May 26, 2010

[This Mama Loves ](http://mamalovesherbargains.com/)respects your privacy.

This Mama Loves Her Bargains and its affiliates may use cookies to store information about your preferences and other information. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and This Mama Loves does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers. Some advertising partners may use cookies. Some of the partners include, but not limited to Groupon, Ebates and GlamMedia. This Mama Loves is not responsible for information obtained from affiliates.

This Mama Loves  is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

This Mama Loves  may on occasion ask for personal information, such as for giveaways. This information will not be sold or used for any purpose other than  contacting the winner of the giveaway. Your information may be sent to giveaway providers for mailing the giveaway. This Mama Loves   is not responsible for information shared with giveaway sponsors as a means of mailing a giveaway. It is the intent of This Mama Loves that this information be colleted for confirming winners of a giveaway as a method of prize distribution only.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

_This privacy policy was written with the help of[ MrsMoneysaver’s policy ](http://www.mrsmoneysaver.com/disclosure/)and [The Coupon Challenge](http://thecouponchallenge.com/)._
